relaxnews
relaxnews
it's really blondel galls i'm the
我真的是金发gall
director of the clipse foundation
Clipse基金会主任
Europe
欧洲
before we started nothing but claude
在我们开始无所事事之前
native java me wonder why mme royal
我的本地Java我想知道为什么mme royal
giving talk your samsung nc10 de fact
实话实说三星nc10
that we have dozens of project
我们有几十个项目
sleep foundation that are not related to
与...无关的睡眠基础
be said ok ok my passing we have
可以说，好的，我过去了
more than three hundred fifty project
三百五十多个项目
eclipse foundation and supported by two
蚀基础，由两个人支撑
hundred eighty members by members
一百八十会员
means that company sativa some money
意味着公司可得一些钱
every year to support at operation one
每年支持一号手术
we have some people around the world
我们在世界各地都有一些人
in north america
在北美
support
熊
yes l aps fifteen bredes developers
是的，我支持15个布雷德开发人员
employees hold up project and one
员工承担项目和一项
day has come back to that letter warns
那天回到那封信警告
people search team members of the
的人员搜寻小组成员
foundation and not really developing
基础而不是真正发展
eclipse project we are doing something
蚀项目，我们正在做某事
How to get an example?
如何举个例子？
bots you there dominate this we have we have
您在那里的机器人主导了我们拥有的
a lot of town of technology
很多技术之乡
weave van wijk you to visit aliotti de
编织van wijk您参观阿利奥蒂德
your free scientific dr clips
您免费的科学博士剪辑
to allow bagdad to view at a
允许巴格达观看
data processing visualization location
数据处理可视化位置
take that location aware technology
采用该位置感知技术
open mdm and something that you will
打开mdm以及您将要执行的操作
never know what the project is
永远不知道项目是什么
automotive and we have several severo
汽车，我们有几个
projects in automotive anao since last
自上次以来在汽车anao中的项目
year we have you
年我们有你
jakarta 1 which is something you think
雅加达1这是你认为的东西
big big morphose djahi community one jump
大morphose djahi社区一跳
at the pier and started long time gone here
在码头，开始很长一段时间去这里
eclipse ali but just to be clear that
蚀阿里，但要清楚一点
now where there is platform for open
现在有开放的平台
innovation and collaboration is a body
创新与协作是一个整体
lot except different domains at the team
很多，除了团队中的不同领域
member foundation i'm not developer and
会员基金会，我不是开发人员，
we have lot except ex developers
除前开发人员外，我们还有很多
what do i do we are providing from a
我该怎么办？
infrastructure to hell pis for the
地狱pis的基础设施
collaborator gather sow gesture south
合作者收集母猪手势向南
is rated May 7 life everything is ok you can
被评为5月7日，生活一切正常，您可以
create your project and bitter bang
创建您的项目，痛苦不已
regrettable was born to this effort
遗憾的是这种努力的诞生
collaboration with weekly better when i
当我与每周更好地合作
was when the story 15 years ago
那是15年前的故事
and having fun with bug tracker
并与错误跟踪器一起玩
repositories wekiss mailing list
存储库wekiss邮件列表
everything that was very mme broten you
一切都让我伤透了你
have an important statistic
有重要的统计数据
n even if we water project work and get
即使我们为项目工作浇水并得到
up saviat with lips project ostier date
与嘴唇项目上更好的约会
github
github上
we steal mirror everything honor to
我们偷走一切荣誉的镜子
infrastructure etc to the widgets for
基础设施等到小部件
freedom freedom fighters this week end
自由战士本周结束
everything from what we have in his
我们所拥有的一切
infrastructure we also sweet community
基础设施我们也是甜蜜的社区
development and you guys and will
发展，你们，并将
participate to evans where there was
参加那里的埃文斯
yes ah yes with boston state and as we
是啊，是与波士顿州一样
be happy to meet you there a we do we
很高兴在那里见到你，我们做到了
have the big tasci this process and
有很大的tasci这个过程，
governance so we have clips
治理，所以我们有剪辑
process development as your place
过程开发作为您的位置
this place to all eclipse eclipse
这个地方所有的日食
project yes to come to trial 7 to 8 10
是的，要进行审判7至8 10
price bit-bed richie eclipse foundation
价格位床里奇日食基金会
process specifications this we have
我们拥有的工艺规范
something to create open-source
创建开源的东西
specifications came to trial
规格开始试用
that is not completely one thing
那不完全是一回事
for more than they knew that
比他们知道的更多
synchronoss restraint process so i know
同步抑制过程，所以我知道
that every year and that says eclipse ali
每年，那说蚀阿里
publishes a news release is now
现在发布新闻稿
since eclipse chair that was
由于日食椅是
published in june we decided to move that
我们在6月发表的文章中决定将其
everything is gray quartz media any price
一切都是灰色石英媒体，任何价格
to the process of life all clips
生活中的所有片段
his books 7.7 me something that had had
他的书7.7告诉我
some point merry is in different forms
一点快乐是不同的形式
will also apply to do jakarta example a
也将适用于做雅加达的例子
one one detailed in terms of governance
一一详细的治理
there is no 1 specific rights must be
没有1项特定权利
to do specific but even brusheau first
做特定但首先
and at ibm credit crunch clipse
在ibm信贷紧缩中
longtime go see the same rights and
长时间去看同样的权利，
beauty satie other members of the new
美女赛迪新成员
world order of the big big playoffs
大季后赛的世界秩序
players on the back or p3 fifty cent in
背面的玩家或p3中的百分之五十
dollars
美元
it's game side of the board of
这是游戏板的一面
directors and the board of directors
董事和董事会
absolutely no in france and technical
在法国和技术上绝对没有
of the six young people on the project this
这个项目的六个年轻人中
technical and technical of the six young
六个年轻人的技术
this project has taken by the developer
该项目已由开发人员承担
himself and by the project leader
他本人和项目负责人
world of director of the ring and stalin
指环王和斯大林导演的世界
me go drive in France or you wish to
我去法国开车，或者你想
take direction live and steam in haiti at
在海地以现场直播和蒸汽
a jacket in een artificial intelligence
人工智能的外套
and specific project this project team is
这个项目团队的具体项目是
complicate the independence in charge
负责独立变得复杂
of taking the jesus and finally
接受耶稣，最后
intellectual property management
知识产权管理
the intellectual property management is
知识产权管理是
very important that you pretty brunette
你这个黑发很重要
process that something the developer
处理开发者的东西
do not like to do and we have team
不喜欢做，我们有团队
dedicated to that and we say this title
致力于这个，我们说这个标题
series inini collaboration between our
我们之间的系列inini合作
team and development team to make
团队和开发团队
sure that a basic lee everything i do
确保我做的一件基本的李
not from an eclipse mistake of can
不是因为罐头的日食错误
it's free creed project center benefits
这是免费的信条项目中心的好处
that's really ordine volunteers the
那是真正的整理志愿者
creation of business provided iko system
创建业务提供的iko系统
external beston siebel platforms has us
外部beston siebel平台拥有我们
say go there the system
说去那里的系统
yes this senate plugin ok prentice
是的，这个参议院插件确定
Guinean plenty of application are
几内亚有很多应用
take advantage of it in we have other examples
在其他例子中利用它
like eclipse figures example claude bez
像日食数字示例克劳德·贝兹
at 10 10 ski my place everything is the must
在10 10滑雪我的地方，一切都是必须的
have read the foundation and that's all
已经阅读了基础，仅此而已
so a bevel eclipse public license
斜面蚀公共许可证
a ritual process people to brighton's
人们去布赖顿的仪式过程
platform and product of the platform
平台和平台产品
even if we have 10 business friendly
即使我们有10位商务人士
approach iphone it is necessary in any members
iPhone的方法，任何成员都必须
to big business with technology it's
用技术去做大生意
at the tea party clipse we are here open
在茶会上，我们在这里开放
source like unity will open source
像团结一样的资源将开源
committee and means that we have fruits
委员会，意味着我们有成果
korval is using his first one is transparent
科尔瓦尔正在使用他的第一个透明
if it's true things that happens in
如果是真的，
project should be free kids in one of
项目应该是其中之一的免费孩子
the public media project melingui which
梅林圭公共媒体项目
project kahn falling and then they can not
项目卡恩下降，然后他们不能
stop participating openness eclipse
停止参与开放日食
The project is open to everyone
该项目向所有人开放
foundation and z and few if you do not
基础和z，如果不这样做，则很少
'managed winter in project ten here
'在这里管理冬季项目十
to help winter in the wall
帮助冬天在墙上
it's only with meritocracy either
要么只有英才
everybody cannes participate all project
大家戛纳参加所有项目
but you have to prove that they used by
但您必须证明他们使用了
contributing to many sporting bugs
导致许多运动错误
sending small contribution and then you
发送少量捐款，然后您
directed by the current
由当前指导
committers of the project to joy
项目的提交者感到高兴
projectim is very important enterprise
Projectim是非常重要的企业
to everything so now after shorts
短裤之后现在一切都这样
what we do when we work
我们工作时会做什么
foundation
基金会
let's go back to claude nativi jara and
让我们回到claude nativi jara
why we say that the future of creative
为什么我们说创意的未来
giles open for the last would locate
最后打开的吉尔斯会找到
say we have more
说我们还有更多
can be seen as fitting in the cloud
可以看作是适合云计算
native java is approaching be started with
本机Java即将开始
vertex be done this project lead the
顶点完成这个项目领导
witcher is reactive active fresh working
巫师是反应活跃新鲜工作
in java zen openline and mackerel
在Java zen openline和鲭鱼中
profile his open jeans sgv mn macro
剖析他的开放式牛仔裤sgv mn宏
profile a
剖析
for enterprise giova macro service is
对于企业giova宏服务是
and the latest adds up all ten
最新的十个加起来
stadiums that's what jakarta at let me tell
这就是雅加达的体育馆
you few words for eclipse open chennai
你为日食打开几句话
under eclipse open genzyme
在日食开放基因酶下
this second date was that has been
第二次约会是
develops in France beginning bbm everything
在法国发展，开始BBM一切
a feminine touch it's decided to
女人味的决定
publish and an open source
发布和开源
josette not just new jersey but you
乔塞特不仅是新泽西人，还有你
have been there for ever the new thing
永远在那里新事物
that and it's in open source project
那是在开源项目中
is due to the thunder license
是由于雷电许可证
eclipse public license gpl fast where it is
Eclipse公共许可证gpl快速在哪里
class no exception and it as good
全班也不例外，它一样好
characteristics and few consider cloud
特点，很少考虑云
native jabba bkc was alone in the memory
本地的贾巴bkc独自在记忆中
footprint a fast start up times so if
占用时间短，因此启动时间短，
you have serve macro services is
您提供的宏服务是
stable
稳定
open text and faster
打开文字更快
service account you means that a memory
服务帐户，您的意思是记忆
then you will say something like
然后你会说类似
you can not know
你不知道
go in the website and you will find
进入网站，您会发现
results of the benchmark 10 10 10 open
基准测试结果10 10 10开放
jeans hine and roses and absorbs by the end of
牛仔裤，玫瑰花和玫瑰花，到年底吸收
presentation from steeve poulin aux
斯蒂夫·波林·奥克斯的演讲
team organizations this crowd me more
团队组织使我更加拥挤
details can be six to ten when he at
当他在时，细节可以是六到十
fitur for example is very interesting
例如，fitur非常有趣
instead of having the class is in
而不是上课
all you do currington 6n you can do
你能做的所有卡宁顿6n
class schering even in between
即使在两者之间也要上课
continence sauvette style sum summoned
失控的自助餐式召唤
mauritius and ving and good for cloud folio
毛里求斯和韦恩，有利于云保护
deployment and you can get it so you can
部署就可以了，因此您可以
get it from adopt open chile / chi dotnet
通过采用开放式智利/ chi dotnet获得它
so i was there it ok you can all
所以我在那里就可以了
to channel i want you want to download
频道我想你要下载
insight and choose from java virtual
洞察力并从Java虚拟中选择
machine to basic lee young is open
基本的李年轻的机器是开放的
djelic is more hot spot open jeep us
djelic是更多的热点吉普车我们
open jean hine you do johan audit
打开让·海因，你去做约翰审计
stael it and you have been taken and
保持它，你已经被带走，
drown a mischievous tease eclipse mike at
淹死了一个调皮的逗食日食麦克
prophet saw the gods duke choice awards
先知看见了众神公爵选择奖
the last recital khourdoian
最后一次独奏音乐会
eclipse macro profile in open-source
Eclipse宏配置文件中的开源
community of people organization
人民团体组织
software vendor want to collaborate in
软件供应商希望合作
eclipse project to define specifications
蚀项目以定义规格
for enterprise java micro service
用于企业Java微服务
liberty sounds t he paillard at micro for
自由听起来微不足道，
you can get the implementation
你可以得到实现
of resources
资源
this verse our specifications c and
这节经文我们的规范c和
support
支持
and i really stuff co organization a
我真的很喜欢合作组织
fortune
财富
in this entry
在此条目
gry joined the death project lease at this
格里在这里加入了死亡项目租赁
that leaders and supporting soa
领导者和支持者
red mike profile
红迈克简介
specifications so what is eclipse
规格，那么什么是日食
macrophages basic liszt started with
巨噬细胞基本病学始于
10 this offer to specifications
10此优惠符合规格
sidiailles jason pidgeon says jack is
sidiailles jason pidgeon说杰克是
right now on google you you see that
现在在Google上，您会看到
it's what you need to create jobs macro
这是您创建作业宏所需要的
micro services engine scene after that
之后的微服务引擎场景
was a with the release of a
是与发布的
approach the holden ead works
接近霍尔顿·埃德作品
specific non-functional property and
特定的非功能性属性和
especially need to my nature you macro
特别需要我本性
services soa difficult escape to get the
服务很难逃脱
result is my cros service still
结果是我的cros服务仍然
walking metrics with default metrics
具有默认指标的步行指标
beatles at applications level metrics
甲壳虫在应用程序级别的指标
fault tolerant this type i call if you if
容错这种类型，如果您
you have chain of my service cros sanyo
您有我的服务连锁店cros sanyo
canada nothing to fear example that the
加拿大无所畏惧的例子
breaker circuit on stuff like that
诸如此类的断路器电路
open racing for service strong racing
公开竞速服务强力竞速
between between long service this
之间长期服务这
shane open service and worst terrorists
Shane开放服务和最严重的恐怖分子
clients' so you see that is mostly 7
客户的，所以您看到的大部分是7
except to note changes a man
除了注意换一个男人
windows 7 sofa notation need
Windows 7沙发符号需要
everything you need at any price there is
您需要的一切，不计任何价格
create wan macros services
创建wan宏服务
interesting stuff with micro eclipse
蚀与有趣的东西
profile that it's really lightweight
它非常轻巧的配置文件
process to define you specifications a
定义规格的过程
tipi hill nowadays vertex team will do
蒂皮·希尔如今的顶点团队将做
dated
日期
the ipad collaborated thing you speak for
您所说的ipad协作产品
reactive streaming programming in my mind
我心中的反应式流式编程
about find and so that is that when i
关于寻找，那就是当我
wanted to mansion vertex watches which
想豪宅的顶点手表
will be the art of french implementation
将是法国实施的艺术
provide everything
提供一切
you need to
你需要
everything is really responsive programming
一切都是响应式编程
reactive stream
反应流
so that very light weight polyglot
这样重量很轻的杂音
framework this event missed one of our
框架此事件错过了我们之一
complicated blocking at micro synchronoss
微同步时的复杂阻塞
service so you can not go to michael
服务，所以你不能去迈克尔
profile of you and if you're so right to
您的个人资料，如果您对
e mailing list
邮件列表
then you will see signs or
那么您将看到迹象或
responsive streaming mode specifications
响应式流模式规范
programming inaction a felony jakarta
编程无为重罪雅加达
it's ok the thur to taiwan harvest or
台湾收成还可以
gather west ibm red hat and the other
聚集西ibm红色帽子和另一个
giovanni partners announcement is so moult
乔凡尼合伙人公告是如此的倒霉
move giovanni in open source
在开源中移动giovanni
under the stewardship of sleep
在睡眠的指导下
foundation with the goal of making
建立目标的基础
it rajan word more open and movement jump
它的rajan词更加开放，运动跳跃
since last year
自去年以来
work the causes moving giovanni from
工作的原因将乔万尼从
some things that is completely managed
一些完全管理的事情
by to something that is complicated open
通过复杂的东西
source and minsk racing something like
源和明斯克赛车像
for new project with one bracci
一个布拉奇的新项目
ninety nine guitry positive committers
九十九guitry积极的提交者
and also 10 of bill pipe lines done
并完成了10条票据管道
fifty three jenkinson steenkiste billpay
五十三个詹金森青少年账单
jenkins the right time to create for
詹金斯在适当的时候创造
release engineering you are huge and
发布工程，您非常庞大，
represent fifteen fourteen person of the
代表十五个人的
eclipse foundation release activities
蚀基础释放活动
and also hold up project that has passed
并保持已经通过的项目
the intellectual property duo leads
知识产权二人组领导
heaven is everything prepared by brick
天堂是用砖头准备的一切
orange and 10 degrees job all
橙色和10度工作
to make it happen this mine that our
为了使这个矿发生
eyes of intellectual property management
知识产权管理的眼光
team serves wedgwood exit recent death
队服务韦奇伍德退出最近死亡
peace of software in the full year in
全年的软件安全性
the full year of high twenty seventeen
高二十七的全年
josette lord of the loss of software
乔塞特勋爵的软件丢失
water sophie activity and here is status
自来水活动，这里是状态
sow all the owls exit nine offers
播种所有猫头鹰退出九个提议
afghan steps of oak is public proposes
阿富汗的橡木台阶被公众提议
also proposed yes yes initial design
也建议是是初始设计
committers of the project x and google
X和Google项目的提交者
cooptent other elect to errors
让其他人选择犯错误
committed on that date will johnson
承诺在该日期约翰逊
the project of the project
项目的项目
will with all the resources unites all
将以所有资源团结所有
collaborated on github you get up project
在github上合作，您可以启动项目
e mailing list this bug tracker and
通过电子邮件发送此错误跟踪器列表，以及
everything and there is the initial
一切都有初始
contribution nichol contribution mind
贡献力
that the owner of the project
该项目的所有者
intellectual property t have to put
知识产权必须投入
together instead on 611 sausages
一起放在611香肠上
all his clips foundation and then the
他所有的剪辑基础，然后
cloud foundations will review the
云基金会将审查
intellectual property and when it's ok
知识产权以及何时可以
we know where it comes from we know that
我们知道它来自哪里，我们知道
the people who could have
有可能的人
right to publish it in open source
公开发布的权利
10:10 conditions so you can not touch
10:10的条件，所以你不能碰
local all positive guitry
本地所有积极指导
and then you are in the working in
然后你在工作中
eclipse foundation repositories status
蚀基金会仓库状态
and if you look at 10 status satis the
如果您看10个状态令人满意
current status everything now is it is
当前状态现在是
working in eclipse chains
在日食链中工作
repositories this it means that all
存储库，这意味着所有
project i'll have been migrating ty all
我将一直在迁移的项目
its clips servers and the community and
它的剪辑服务器和社区，以及
start collaborating in 2nd project and
开始在第二个项目中进行合作，
now the next up is here
现在下一个在这里
you to create the first official review
您创建第一个正式评论
official willy cording touzit eclipse
官方Willy Cording Touzit日食
process development
工艺开发
so that for the technical door is said
所以说技术门
organizational door
组织门
we have the jakarta globe king group
我们有雅加达环球大帝集团
what is the jakarta ring globe done
雅加达环地球仪做了什么
approve specifications and 15 still in
批准规格，还有15个仍在
oz is a pretty raid specs
盎司是一个不错的突袭规格
management java community process surfer
管理Java社区流程冲浪者
glassfish and supplementation
玻璃鱼和补品
technology compatibility kit what's
技术兼容性套件是什么
really interesting and moving java
真的很有趣，移动的Java
jakarta is not only glassfish is
雅加达不仅是玻璃鱼
open source
开源
she foams the whole team are some
她使整个团队充满活力
stars is open source you are note
星星是开源的，请注意
big big difference of technology
技术差异大
compatibility leaves to open source
兼容性留给开源
engine for all the specifications will
所有规格的引擎
be made in open source
开源
wade co yezh jakarta
韦德（Yade）雅加达
to the specifications manager this jakarta
给雅加达规格经理
ibres and goes wild new brain
不知所措，疯狂新大脑
so it means that he will we protect
所以这意味着他将保护我们
the wind that has value to be not every
有价值的风不是每一个
body will be able to it's ok ayem
身体可以没事了
jakarta complained go as back to
雅加达抱怨回去
that let her and also established
让她也建立了
technical roadmap causes yes they
技术路线图是的，他们
want even if it be com / open and
想要即使它是com / open和
more at giles we still need to have some
我们还需要一些帮助
ntsama coordination
ntsama协调
bitter virgin to where it is going
苦涩的处女
front of our sun shines body channel
我们的阳光照耀着身体的通道
audited sites good thing at road inc
经审核的现场道路公司的好事
ok software windows enterprise system
好的软件Windows企业系统
integrators we also have they want
集成商，我们也有他们想要的
java user group this java java community
java用户组此java java社区
went to giacometti darjeeling
去了giacometti darjeeling
10 and ford
10和福特
if you look at the jakarta
如果你看雅加达
globe king of members of the left side
左侧成员的环球之王
we have with the usual suspects sodat
我们与通常的嫌疑人苏打
companies this java me enterprise saddle
公司此java me企业鞍
louwers so gay to ibm fujitsu rikers
大声招呼同志向ibm富士通rikers
red hat to thurso nicetoile smaller
红色的帽子，以thurso nicetoile较小
companies like paillard anatomy tribe
像Paillard的解剖部落的公司
cause it's also one of the
因为它也是其中之一
value of our open source iko system to
我们的开源iko系统的价值
big x12 big big fish is with the
大x12大大鱼是与
smaller fishes to make their work
较小的鱼来工作
together to participate side and we have
一起参加聚会，我们有
london java community for example
例如伦敦Java社区
pivotal is a member because if you think
关键是成员，因为如果您认为
about spring most of the spring hill
大约春天，整个春天山
house of jamaica carta specifications n
牙买加Carta规格的房屋
another example louis admitted or me do
路易斯承认的另一个例子还是我
is being so that the japanese
这样日本人
bankanywhere working with her
与她一起工作的银行
you are people in london and there are
你是伦敦的人，有
using lot except cavalli and they want to
使用很多，除了cavalli，他们想
participate to jakarta and because they
参加雅加达，因为他们
want twinject it's requirements and i
要缠绕它的要求，我
want you to include it's hard and shaun
希望您加入其中，这很困难
of the space fixation on what does it
固定装置的作用
mean headdress is here that is open source
意思是头饰在这里是开源的
and visceral few days before when using
使用前几天和内脏
the one i wanted to ticket access
我想进入门票的那个
must all-public this weekend in
必须在这个周末全部公开
the other of tichy quai duquesne start
tichy quai duquesne的另一个开始
running the chicken study was in what in
进行鸡研究是在什么
the canon test if some things not
佳能测试是否有些事情不
running the expected the can even things
运行预期的甚至可以的东西
is ok but be that the mirror a good
可以，但要是镜子好
merit food her heroine this
值得食物她的女主人公这
test something new to have the ticket
测试新的东西来获得门票
open source and canes looking to it can
开源和期待它的手杖可以
understand what is to which is supposed
了解应该做什么
to work
工作
you can also not get cheap show sing
你也不能得到便宜的表演唱歌
sing and the fate more open sharing the
唱歌，命运更开放，分享
responsibility of managing edmonton in
管理埃德蒙顿的责任
the chicken and the last portlets
鸡肉和最后的portlet
neutrality battles with the continuity to the
中立性与
n186 is vast
n186广阔
we saw stay projects in die eclipse
我们看到食宿项目
ecosystems where some of the actors of
一些参与者的生态系统
the project were switching toulouse
该项目正在切换图卢兹
priorities made
优先事项
oignies web project is useful a
Oignies Web项目很有用
necessary for love loss
失去爱的必要
other factors which they pin and it's ok
他们确定的其他因素也可以
said everything
说的一切
need to be wild at heart
需要内心发狂
important
重要
a disco is this event here
这里是迪斯科舞厅
what will be be more sustaining 510
510年将更可持续
open-source sauzereau map
开源sauzereau地图
we started with harvesting glassfish file
我们从收获玻璃鱼档案开始
on penalties I had something
受罚我有一些东西
complete and by the end of the year
年底完成
it will be eclipse glassfish five the
这将是蚀玻璃鱼五
one show and is there java there is compliance
一场演出，那里有java吗？
so that the result of moving everything
这样移动一切的结果
under the stewardship of sleep
在睡眠的指导下
foundation
基金会
this community start working and eclipse
这个社区开始工作并黯然失色
glassfish five of all eclipse thanks
所有的日食中的五个
fault sheet of all yes bias
是偏见的故障表
full young jakarta there is said
据说有年轻的雅加达人
benezeth will be at the step wars moving of
benezeth将步步为营
source code a new state and setting up
源代码的新状态和设置
new processes for hope for
希望的新过程
specifications n guesso jakarta i hate
规格我猜雅加达我讨厌
that will still be something very
那仍然是非常非常的东西
similar to the day by day all our friends
类似于我们所有的朋友
then it's time when everything will
然后是时候一切都会
start
启动
evolving more quickly a when you
不断发展，当您
will see in to innovations that will
将看到创新
that will be in jectif jakarta yili nine
那将在雅加达宜力九
elite jakarta n1 the promise the
雅加达精英n1的承诺
commitment of all the actors helps
所有演员的承诺有助于
and will go fast to date time
并会快速更新时间
what was happening before 1,2 to will it
在1,2之前发生了什么
work will it be more open
工作会更开放吗
stand since i eclipse foundation
自从我超越基金会以来就站起来
process specifications of
工艺规格
process specifications and write down their
工艺规范并写下他们的
different from the and clips
与和剪辑不同
development process is offered to the tp ok
开发过程提供给TP OK
jazz to create new specifications you
爵士创造新的规格你
you have to publish to get some
您必须发布才能获得一些
interest in the community and then we
对社区感兴趣，然后我们
believe you and you will have space
相信你，你将有空间
work and you and your specifications
工作，你和你的规格
lamb develops and specifications
羔羊的发展和规格
can create milestones bet at home.com
可以在home.com上创建里程碑投注
want to create release of your
想要创建您的发布
specifications late final jump to
规格后期最终跳转到
specifications and then you will go
规格，然后你会去
smiles of easy review 1,800 beasts of
容易回顾的微笑1,800只野兽
sum sum stuff ignals line to
总和东西ignals行到
Next side specifications of new star
新星的下侧规格
of new music of the new single plane
新单飞机的新音乐
of the public planes of what you want to do
您想做什么的公共飞机
and development scene cording to the
和发展场景与
planes and you with so what is it to
飞机和你在一起，那是什么
release specifications so in
发布规范
specifications will have documentation
规格将有文件
soad this text
涂上这段文字
will have some technical artifacts this
将有一些技术工件
spice annotations from the top less than we
顶部的香料注释比我们少
will have this i quai n so we need
我要有这个，所以我们需要
compatible implementation we and more
兼容的实现我们等等
than that swing and our punishments source
比那个秋千和我们的惩罚源
compatible implementation sow want you
兼容的实现母猪想要你
have everything you have you willis
拥有你拥有的一切
candidate and then you want to promote
候选人，然后你想提升
it has the release on hewitt ghost rider
它已经发布了休伊特幽灵骑士
review and then they find her
审查，然后他们找到她
specifications this text ribi near
规范此文本ribi附近
reading and technical artifact you will
阅读和技术文物，您将
have access only all inzaghi binaries
只能访问所有inzaghi二进制文件
biesheim binaries one before you
比斯海姆二进制文件在您之前
specifications become steiner unit wav
规格成为斯坦纳单位
and least one compatit want a premium
至少有一个竞争对手想要溢价
and nation under one of the line 6
和国家在第6行之一
accepted by sleep foundation
被睡眠基金会接受
bs says patxi you are seduced view
bs说patxi你被诱惑
picture of all we make sure that it is
所有图片，我们确保它是
open a room the gutters love more
开个房间，天沟更爱
quickly threshous style we want that
快速的脱粒风格，我们想要的是
hockey when you have finally
曲棍球，当你终于
specifications you keep our love to
规格，您一直爱我们
bias want everything everything said clear is
偏要一切都说清楚
ok iam compliance with this version of
确定我符合此版本的
the specifications so what i knew what
规格，所以我知道什么
similar to the previous process in java
类似于Java中的上一个过程
community process and 3 specifications
社区流程和3个规范
frost &amp; you start to specifications
霜冻，你开始规格
then we will see implemented jakarta
然后我们将看到实施的雅加达
esata or trust you start with good
esata或相信您从好的开始
then you're right specification is
那么你正确的规范是
static explains what in the good
静态解释了什么是好的
the ship in of lead specifications
船的铅规格
adverys tung position with i world
与世界同盟
holdings of grief and backbone all the
所有的悲伤和骨气
intellectual property of the
的知识产权
specifications a jakarta and 10
规格雅加达和10
collaborative everybody keeps and
每个人都保持协作
intellectuals pro porter n basic n
基本知识分子
it means that this specification is open
这意味着该规范是开放的
and an open source
和一个开源
some things are similar bike it's jessy
有些东西和自行车很相似
pi have been public
pi已公开
communication since the beginning
从一开始就沟通
we will continue and this audience
我们将继续，这个观众
communication because every transparent
沟通，因为每个透明
document
文件
I anticipated cannes by claude source
我曾预测claude来源的戛纳电影节
insee jessy pi ca
见杰西·皮卡
mandatory open source and monitoring to
强制性开源和监控
have a hundred documents anticipated if
如果有一百份文件，
open source and jakarta between our
我们之间的开源和雅加达
lines
线
in the jessy
在杰西
reference implantation on ice sheet
冰盖上的参考植入
jakarta we want one or more compatible
雅加达，我们想要一个或多个兼容
implementation at least one
实施至少一项
open-source combative and
开源好斗和
the implementation so why we now so
实施，为什么我们现在如此
work hall i call if contributed to
我打电话给工作间
his clips are young
他的剪辑很年轻
glassfish eclipse ice fikda this fish
玻璃鱼月食冰fikda这条鱼
five of antoine took ten candidates it was
五分之一的安托万拿了十个候选人
published just before that at customs
在那之前在海关发表
eclipse can we expect to be in is working
月食，我们可以预期会在工作吗
hard to end the creeps team
难以结束小兵团队
as to release eclipse glassfish five
至于释放日食玻璃鱼五
by this number four kings 3
四位国王3
eclipse foundation process specifications
月食基础工艺规范
that has been reviewed by the community
已经社区审核过
and we have for specific and news
我们有具体的新闻
in it so we are testing in my life with
在其中，所以我们正在用
jakarta hinault website to another
雅加达hinault网站到另一个
thing to you definitive is jakarta
最终的决定是雅加达
hinault sequels like djiby sy for you
像dbyby sy这样的hinault续集为您
know sequel at nancy quell database sow
在南希·克尔数据库母猪中了解续集
itunes movie is open it really open
iTunes电影是打开的，它真的是打开的
Asked for you we started to listen
问你我们开始听
to the community services exercise a
到社区服务运动
he laughs October at any price people
他不惜一切代价欢笑十月
answer to catch your death to some
回答你的死亡
generic christine before orichalcum
Orichalcum前的通用克里斯汀
at customs
在海关
an eclipse conne n in which we sing
在其中唱歌的月食连接
seventy four answers to the christians
基督徒的七十四个答案
sow ips
播种ips
ok to southern rosa hockey we want more
好的，我们要南部罗莎曲棍球
more we chavalon
我们更多
guen modularity improvement in jakarta
雅加达的guen模块性改进
macro service 6 1 claude servers less
宏服务6 1个较少的服务器
and also the community wants to be
社区也希望成为
involved in the good news that are
涉及到的好消息是
willing 7th crown you're clip the
愿意为您冠上第七冠
current jakarta esteem is ready to
目前的雅加达尊重已准备就绪
welcome new people ok we are still a
欢迎新朋友，好吧，我们仍然是
transition line 'sometimes vocal the
过渡线有时
focus is we need to do this
重点是我们需要这样做
blend of the year we need to start
我们需要从这一年开始
jakarta and process specifications goes
雅加达和工艺规范去
be ok to be ok
没事没事
there i need this way needs to make me
那里我需要这种方式需要让我
successfull with the wind jakarta
随风雅加达成功
that's open for participation in
开放参与
innovations to be jakarta i to be the
创新成为雅加达，我成为
where
哪里
yes design and develop the future of
是的，设计和发展未来
native klub jabba matta e mailing list
本地klub jabba matta e邮件列表
cristiano stupid creation stars and
克里斯蒂亚诺愚蠢的创作明星和
queens of others and then he
别人的皇后，然后他
started contributing to contributing
开始贡献自己的力量
aydius all alone
艾迪乌斯一个人
[Music]
[音乐]
every time i will ask for every time
每次我都会要求
i link to to google docs scene in this
我在此链接到google docs场景
mailing list within an entire invitation
整个邀请中的邮件列表
participation
参与
is this an invitation to participate in
这是参加邀请吗
your eyes be shorter than expected
你的眼睛比预期的短
slovenia cristian abbiati roofing
斯洛文尼亚cristian abbiati屋顶
Jakarta was king
雅加达为国王
if it emanates except javari psg in
如果它发出，除了javari psg
cherry tree as far as zain at the parade
游行队伍中最远的樱桃树
everything is movement towards snow and we
一切都在朝着雪运动，我们
also plan to have racing that need to
也计划有赛车需要
be you look so so here
你在这里看起来好吗
ok they were coming up djiby raise money
好吧，他们来了吉比筹集资金
holder stuff like or herbie saurai party
持有人之类的东西或Herbie Saurai Party
draws end of course
当然结束了
atchoum paint we need to be more in
漆我们需要更多
order to be more innovative
为了更具创新性
have to odds and ends and are
不得不零头，并且是
good stuff
好东西
yeah so 5 so it goes our strengths
是的，所以5就是我们的长处
but my jersey of astana gazette and
但是我的阿斯塔纳公报球衣
livry djazaïri specifications you have
您拥有的livrydjazaïri规格
minimum java ee 6 version need to be
最低Java EE 6版本需要
supported a think that will be
支持的想法是
something similar with a jakarta and
雅加达的东西和
specifications and the series friends
规格及系列朋友
minimum lts verchenova here this need to
最小lts verchenova在这里，这需要
be supported by not let this
得到支持，不要让这个
next season and zou and yes the web
下个季节，邹，是的，网上
logic application server full offer
逻辑应用服务器的完整报价
things happen to recall
回想起事情
product marketing product management
产品营销产品管理
announcement and reason why not date style
公告以及为什么不采用日期样式的原因
follow up of all the way i so sexy and
一直跟着我这么性感，
then using weblogic from date show askew
然后从日期开始使用weblogic显示歪斜
weblogic contact what planes hockey
weblogic联系什么飞机曲棍球
5.01 and you are where you go
5.01，您在哪里
sweet albi conversation
甜蜜的阿尔比对话